Francis D. Donovan Papers
© 2011 University of Connecticut
- Series VI: Photographic materials, undated, 1829-1997
  - Subseries A: Prints, undated, 1829-1997
    - Sub-subseries 3: Cars, undated, 1880-1989
      - Holyoke Street Railroad, Mount Tom car, 1915 (Box 30:, Folder 3070)
      - Hul Street Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3071)
      - Kennebec Lewiston Railroad, car 138, 1936 (Box 30:, Folder 3072)
      - Knox Railroad, plow 1, 1935 (Box 30:, Folder 3073)
      - Lincoln Lombards Railroad, steam log hauler, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3074)
      - Linwood Street Railroad, car 4, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3075)
      - Linwood Street Railroad, car 4, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3076)
      - Long Island Railroad, turbine car, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3077)
      - Lowell & Boston Railroad, car 4, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3078)
      - Lowell & Fitchburg Railroad, car 38, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3079)
      - Lowell & Fitchburg Railroad, unidentified plow, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3080)
      - Lynn & Boston Railroad, "High Rock", undated (Box 30:, Folder 3081)
      - Lynn & Boston Railroad, car 70, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3082)
      - Lynn & Boston Railroad, car 224, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3083)
      - Lynn & Boston Railroad, open car 234, 1894 (Box 30:, Folder 3084)
      - Lynn & Boston Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3085)
      - Maine Central Railroad, plow 4, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3086)
      - Maine Central Railroad, plow 14, 1963 (Box 30:, Folder 3087)
      - Maine Central Railroad, plow 30, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3088)
      - Maine Central Railroad, plow 35, 1935 (Box 30:, Folder 3089)
      - Maine Central Railroad, plow 40, 1963 (Box 30:, Folder 3090)
      - Maine Central Railroad, plow 46, 1957 (Box 30:, Folder 3091)
      - Maine Central Railroad, plow 57, 1927 (Box 30:, Folder 3092)
      - Maine Central Railroad, plow 57, 1927 (Box 30:, Folder 3093)
      - Maine Central Railroad, plow 58, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3094)
      - Maine Central Railroad, plow 70, 1936 (Box 30:, Folder 3095)
      - Maine Central Railroad, plow 71, 1962 (Box 30:, Folder 3096)
      - Maine Central Railroad, plow 82, 1963 (Box 30:, Folder 3097)
      - Maine Central Railroad, plow 90, 1961 (Box 30:, Folder 3098)
      - Maine Central Railroad, jordan spreader 799, 1958 (Box 30:, Folder 3099)
      - Maine Central Railroad, plow 1133, 1963 (Box 30:, Folder 3100)
      - Maine Central Railroad, plow 1134, 1938 (Box 30:, Folder 3101)
      - Maine Central Railroad, car 1139, 1962 (Box 30:, Folder 3102)
      - Maine Central Railroad, flanger 1147, 1963 (Box 30:, Folder 3103)
      - Maine Central Railroad, car 1150, 1970 (Box 30:, Folder 3104)
      - Maine Central Railroad, tool car 1303, 1975 (Box 30:, Folder 3105)
      - Manchester Street Railroad, car 44, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3106)
      - Manchester Street Railroad, car 48, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3107)
      - Manson Railroad, plow 1, 1937 (Box 30:, Folder 3108)
      - Marlboro & Westboro Street Railroad, car 20, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3109)
      - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority, car 70, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3110)
      - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority, car 70, undated (Box 30:, Folder 3111)
      - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority, car 3008, 1974 (Box 30:, Folder 3112)
      - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority, car 3048, 1974 (Box 30:, Folder 3113)
      - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority, car 3128, 1968 (Box 30:, Folder 3114)
      - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority, car 3250, 1974 (Box 30:, Folder 3115)
      - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority, car 3252, 1974 (Box 30:, Folder 3116)
      - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority, car 3297, 1974 (Box 30:, Folder 3117)
      - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority, car 5821, 1960 (Box 30:, Folder 3118)
      - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority, car 6309, 1948 (Box 30:, Folder 3119)
      - Massachusetts Bay Transportation Authority, unidentified car, 1966 (Box 30:, Folder 3120)
      - Medway & Dedham Railroad, unidentified car, 1899 (Box 31:, Folder 3121)
      - Milford & Bigbee Railroad, plow 38, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3122)
      - Middlesex & Boston Street Railroad, car 42, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3123)
      - Milford, Attleboro, & Woonsocket Railroad, car 15, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3124)
      - Milford, Attleboro, & Woonsocket Railroad, car 24, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3125)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, open car, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3126)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, line car, 1920 (Box 31:, Folder 3127)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, line car, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3128)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, line car, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3129)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 18, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3130)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 27, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3131)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, cars 27 and 31, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3132)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 28, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3133)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 29, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3134)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 32, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3135)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 32, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3136)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 32, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3137)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 37, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3138)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 87, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3139)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 91, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3140)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 99, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3141)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 101, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3142)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 115, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3143)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 115, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3144)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 117, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3145)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 117, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3146)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, car 4992, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3147)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3148)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3149)
      - Milford & Uxbridge Street Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3150)
      - Milford & Woonsocket Railroad, plow 1, 1933 (Box 31:, Folder 3151)
      - Milford, Holliston & Framingham Railroad, line car 1, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3152)
      - Milford, Holliston & Framingham Railroad, car 2, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3153)
      - Milford, Holliston & Framingham Railroad, car 11, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3154)
      - Milford, Holliston & Framingham Railroad, car 23, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3155)
      - Milford, Holliston & Framingham Railroad, car 23, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3156)
      - Milford, Holliston & Framingham Railroad, car 101, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3157)
      - Milford, Holliston & Framingham Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3158)
      - Minneapolis Street Railroad, car 132, 1885 (Box 31:, Folder 3159)
      - Mount Hope Industries Railroad, mack shifter, 1965 (Box 31:, Folder 3160)
      - Mount Mansfield Electric Railroad, car 1, 1921 (Box 31:, Folder 3161)
      - Mount Tom Railroad, "Elizur Holyoke", 1907 (Box 31:, Folder 3162)
      - Mount Tom Railroad, "Elizur Holyoke", 1907 (Box 31:, Folder 3163)
      - Mount Tom Railroad, "Elizur Holyoke", 1912 (Box 31:, Folder 3164)
      - Mount Tom Railroad, "Rowland Thomas", 1912 (Box 31:, Folder 3165)
      - Mount Tom Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3166)
      - Nanhant & Lynn Railroad, car 1, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3167)
      - Nantasket Beach Railroad, car 3326, 1920 (Box 31:, Folder 3168)
      - Newburyport & Amesbury Street Railroad, car 34, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3169)
      - Newburyport Car Company Railroad, car 15, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3170)
      - New York Central Railroad, "Hickory Creek", 1948 (Box 31:, Folder 3171)
      - New York Central Railroad, plow x-222, 1898 (Box 31:, Folder 3172)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, coach 0755, 1970 (Box 31:, Folder 3173)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, car 41, 1961 (Box 31:, Folder 3174)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, car 41, 1961 (Box 31:, Folder 3175)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, car 41, 1961 (Box 31:, Folder 3176)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, car 41, 1961 (Box 31:, Folder 3177)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, car 44, circa 1955 (Box 31:, Folder 3178)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, car 85, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3179)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, coach w-187, 1967 (Box 31:, Folder 3180)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, coach w-187, 1966 (Box 31:, Folder 3181)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, section motor cars 999 and B10, 1953 (Box 31:, Folder 3182)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, electric coach 4023, 1946 (Box 31:, Folder 3183)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, electric coach 4023, 1946 (Box 31:, Folder 3184)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, electric coach 4027, 1946 (Box 31:, Folder 3185)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, electric coach 4200, 1946 (Box 31:, Folder 3186)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, car 9015, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3187)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, car 9019, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3188)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, cars 9110 and 9003, 1946 (Box 31:, Folder 3189)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, car 33821, 1960 (Box 31:, Folder 3190)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, box car 65656, 1936 (Box 31:, Folder 3191)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, car 78241, 1935 (Box 31:, Folder 3192)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, box car 78241, 1936 (Box 31:, Folder 3193)
      - New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad, car 82128, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3194)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3195)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3196)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3197)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3198)
      - Norfolk & Western Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3199)
      - Northern Massachusetts Street Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3200)
      - North Woburn Railroad, horse car 6, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3201)
      - Norway & Paris Street Railroad, car 3, 1910 (Box 31:, Folder 3202)
      - Norwich Street Railroad, car 12, 1897 (Box 31:, Folder 3203)
      - Old Colony Railroad, cars 881 and 1962, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3204)
      - Orono Railroad, car 94, 1924 (Box 31:, Folder 3205)
      - Pacific Electric Railroad, car 544, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3206)
      - Pacific Great Eastern Railroad, spreader 303, 1956 (Box 31:, Folder 3207)
      - Pacific Great Eastern Railroad, car 504, 1958 (Box 31:, Folder 3208)
      - Pacific Great Eastern Railroad, car 1877, 1958 (Box 31:, Folder 3209)
      - Pacific Great Eastern Railroad, plow 6001, 1957 (Box 31:, Folder 3210)
      - Pacific Great Eastern Railroad, plow 6003, 1957 (Box 31:, Folder 3211)
      - Pacific Great Eastern Railroad, snow flanger 6015, 1957 (Box 31:, Folder 3212)
      - Peabody, Salem & Beverly Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3213)
      - Peabody, Salem & Beverly Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3214)
      - Portland Railroad, car 175, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3215)
      - Portland Railroad, car 195, 1939 (Box 31:, Folder 3216)
      - Portland Railroad, car 197, 1934 (Box 31:, Folder 3217)
      - Portland Railroad, car 253, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3218)
      - Portland Railroad, car 404, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3219)
      - Portland-Lewiston Interurban Railroad, car 90, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3220)
      - Portland-Lewiston Interurban Railroad, service car 90, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3221)
      - Portsmouth Electric Railroad, car 97, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3222)
      - Quincy & Boston Railroad, car 47, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3223)
      - Quincy & Boston Railroad, car 47, 1896 (Box 31:, Folder 3224)
      - Quincy & Boston Railroad, unidentified car, 1896 (Box 31:, Folder 3225)
      - Rockland & Abington Railroad, car 3703, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3226)
      - Rockland, Thomaston & Camden Railroad, car 3, undated (Box 31:, Folder 3227)
      - Rutland Railroad, freight car, 1962 (Box 32:, Folder 3228)
      - Rutland Railroad, freight car, 1962 (Box 32:, Folder 3229)
      - Rutland Railroad, plow x-102, 1921 (Box 32:, Folder 3230)
      - Rutland Railroad, plow x-104, 1960 (Box 32:, Folder 3231)
      - Rutland Railroad, plow x-115, 1963 (Box 32:, Folder 3232)
      - Rutland Railroad, plow x-180, 1960 (Box 32:, Folder 3233)
      - Sacramento Northern Railroad, car 1005, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3234)
      - Saint Johnsbury & Lake Champlain Railroad, plow 53, 1962 (Box 32:, Folder 3235)
      - Sandy River & Rangeley Lakes Railroad, caboose 501, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3236)
      - Sandy River & Rangeley Lakes Railroad, caboose 504, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3237)
      - Sanford Eastern Railroad, plow 16, 1958 (Box 32:, Folder 3238)
      - Somerset Traction Company Railroad, car 3, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3239)
      - Somerset Traction Company Railroad, car 4, 1928 (Box 32:, Folder 3240)
      - Springfield Electric Railroad, car 5, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3241)
      - Springfield Terminal Railroad, plow 1, 1960 (Box 32:, Folder 3242)
      - Springfield Terminal Railroad, car 20, 1937 (Box 32:, Folder 3243)
      - Taunton & Pawtucket Railroad, car 33, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3244)
      - T.M.C. Railroad, car 10, 1937 (Box 32:, Folder 3245)
      - T.M.C. Railroad, plow 6, 1937 (Box 32:, Folder 3246)
      - Third Avenue Railroad, car 1222, 1940 (Box 32:, Folder 3247)
      - Third Avenue Railroad, car 1225, 1940 (Box 32:, Folder 3248)
      - Union Street Railroad, car 144, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3249)
      - Union Street Railroad, car 226, 1927 (Box 32:, Folder 3250)
      - Union Street Railroad, car 244, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3251)
      - Union Street Railroad, car 244, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3252)
      - Union Street Railroad, car 271, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3253)
      - Union Street Railroad, car 284, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3254)
      - Union Street Railroad, car 293, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3255)
      - Union Street Railroad, car 293, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3256)
      - Union Street Railroad, car 413, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3257)
      - Union Street Railroad, car 605, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3258)
      - Union Street Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3259)
      - United States Military Railroad, locomotive tender, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3260)
      - Waterville, Fairfield & Oakland Railroad, car 44, 1937 (Box 32:, Folder 3261)
      - West End Street Railroad, car 279, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3262)
      - West End Street Railroad, unidentified car, 1895 (Box 32:, Folder 3263)
      - Western Massachusetts Railroad, car 104, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3264)
      - West Roxbury & Roslindale Street Railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3265)
      - White Pass & Yukon Railroad, car 211, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3266)
      - Wood River Railroad, coach 1, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3267)
      - Worcester Consolidated Street Railroad, car 50, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3268)
      - Worcester Consolidated Street Railroad, wilder snow plow, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3269)
      - Worcester Consolidated Street Railroad, wilder snow plow, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3270)
      - Unidentified railroad, British passenger cars in station, undated (Box 28:, Folder 2887)
      - Unidentified railroad, "Lightning Express", undated (Box 32:, Folder 3271)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 0178, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3272)
      - Unidentified railroad, house car, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3273)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 11, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3274)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 11, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3275)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 14, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3276)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 14, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3277)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 15, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3278)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 16, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3279)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 16, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3280)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 21, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3281)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 29, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3282)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 32, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3283)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 33, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3284)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 33, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3285)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 48, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3286)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 60, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3287)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 64, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3288)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 82, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3289)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 85, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3290)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 87, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3291)
      - Unidentified railroad, excursion car 101, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3292)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 102, 1930 (Box 32:, Folder 3293)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 105, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3294)
      - Unidentified railroad, Budd 200, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3295)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 462, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3296)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 475, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3297)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 559, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3298)
      - Unidentified railroad, cars 681 and 1384, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3299)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 836, 1967 (Box 32:, Folder 3300)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 836, 1967 (Box 32:, Folder 3301)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 836, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3302)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 836, 1967 (Box 32:, Folder 3303)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 836, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3304)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 836, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3305)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 836, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3306)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 861, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3307)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 911, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3308)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 911, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3309)
      - Unidentified railroad, street car 1001, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3310)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 1143, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3311)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 1439, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3312)
      - Unidentified railroad, open car 1533, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3313)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 1613, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3314)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 1613, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3315)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 1701, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3316)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 1701, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3317)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 3020, circa 1912 (Box 32:, Folder 3318)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 3051, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3319)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 3128, 1968 (Box 32:, Folder 3320)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 3708, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3321)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 6131, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3322)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 6317, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3323)
      - Unidentified railroad, car 7080, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3324)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified caboose, 1970 (Box 32:, Folder 3325)
      - Unidentified railroad, car E10, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3326)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified plow, 1920 (Box 32:, Folder 3327)
      - Unidentified railroad, plow 3, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3328)
      - Unidentified railroad, plow 9, undated (Box 32:, Folder 3329)
      - Unidentified railroad, gas storage tanks, 1964 (Box 32:, Folder 3330)
      - Unidentified railroad, gas storage tanks, 1964 (Box 33:, Folder 3331)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3332)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3333)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3334)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3335)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3336)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, 1967 (Box 33:, Folder 3337)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3338)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3339)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3340)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3341)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3342)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3343)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3344)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3345)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3346)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3347)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3348)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3349)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3350)
      - Unidentified railroad, unidentified car, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3351)
    - Sub-subseries 4: Railroad Scenes, undated, 1876-1997
      - Employees, Walter R. Figg, 1954 (Box 33:, Folder 3352)
      - Employees, J.H. French, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3353)
      - Employees, Albert Griggs, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3354)
      - Employees, William Mason, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3355)
      - Employees, Joe Page, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3356)
      - Employees, Frank Pearson, circa 1915 (Box 33:, Folder 3357)
      - Employees, Albert Sheldon, 1939 (Box 33:, Folder 3358)
      - Employees, George B. Williams, undated (Box 33:, Folder 3359)
      - Wrecks, Quincy engine 122, 1890 (Box 33:, Folder 3359)
      - Wrecks, Quincy engine 122, 1890 (Box 33:, Folder 3360)
      - Wrecks, Vermont Valley engine 10, 1905 (Box 33:, Folder 3361)
      - Wrecks, Rockfall, Connecticut, 1906 (Box 33:, Folder 3362)
      - Wrecks, Boston & Maine in West Windham, New Hampshire, 1906 (Box 33:, Folder 3363)
      - Wrecks, Boston & Maine in West Windham, New Hampshire, 1906 (Box 33:, Folder 3364)
      - Wrecks, Boston & Maine in West Windham, New Hampshire, 1906 (Box 33:, Folder 3365)
      - Wrecks, Boston & Maine in West Windham, New Hampshire, 1906 (Box 33:, Folder 3366)
      - Wrecks, Boston & Maine in West Windham, New Hampshire, 1906 (Box 33:, Folder 3367)
      - Wrecks, car 34 at West Kennebrink, 1908 (Box 33:, Folder 3368)
      - Wrecks, Boston & Maine engine 827, 1908 (Box 33:, Folder 3369)
      - Wrecks, Portland Train, Saugus Branch Junction, 1910 (Box 33:, Folder 3370)
      - Wrecks, Readville, 1923 (Box 33:, Folder 3371)